(Q1) JAKE: Hello, Junior Cycle camp, Jake speaking.
WOMAN: Hi.
I'm calling for some information about the cycle camp – I'm thinking of sending my son.
JAKE: Great.
Well, it's held every weekday morning over the summer vacation and we focus on basic cycling skills and safety.
We have eight levels for children from three years upwards.
How old's your son?
WOMAN: Charlie?
He's seven.
He can ride a bike, but he needs a little more training before he's safe to go on the road.
[Q1定位句] JAKE: He'd probably be best in Level 5.
[Q1答案句] They start off practising on the site here, and we aim to get them riding on the road, but first they're taken to ride in the park, away from the traffic.
(Q2) WOMAN: Right. And can you tell me a bit about the instructors?
JAKE: Well, all our staff wear different coloured shirts.
[Q2干扰项] So, we have three supervisors, and they have red shirts. They support the instructors, and they also stand in for me if I'm not around.
[Q2答案句] Then the instructors themselves are in blue shirts, and one of these is responsible for each class.
WOMAN: OK.
(Q3) [Q3定位， 跟in order to, have to = ... is required , Q3答案句] JAKE: In order to be accepted, all our instructors have to submit a reference from someone who's seen them work with children – like if they've worked as a babysitter, for example.
Then they have to complete our training course, including how to do lesson plans, and generally care for the well-being of the kids in their class.
They do a great job, I have to say.
(Q4) WOMAN: Right. And tell me a bit about the classes.
What size will Charlie's class be?
JAKE: We have a limit of eight children in each class, so their instructor really gets to know them well.
[Q4定位句 quiet times， Q4答案句] They're out riding most of the time but they have quiet times too, where their instructor might tell them a story that's got something to do with cycling, or get them to play a game together.
It's a lot of fun.
WOMAN: It must be.
(Q5) [Q5答案句， 疑似答案记录 there is【rain】， 后面代词指代了] Now, what happens if there's rain?
Do the classes still run?
JAKE: Oh yes. JAKE：
We don't let that put us off – we just put on our waterproofs and keep cycling.
(Q6) WOMAN: And is there anything special Charlie should bring along with him?
[Q6答案句： snack] JAKE: Well, maybe some spare clothes, especially if the weather's not so good.And a snack for break time.
(Q7) WOMAN: How about a drink?
JAKE: No, we'll provide that. JAKE：
And make sure he has shoes, not sandals.
WOMAN: Sure. WOMAN：
[Q7答案句，听出机会： 紧跟上一行定位词] And just at present Charlie has to take medication every few hours, so I'll make sure he has that.
JAKE: Absolutely.
Just give us details of when he has to take it and we'll make sure he does.
WOMAN: Thanks.
(Q8) JAKE: Now, there are a few things you should know about Day 1 of the camp.
The classes normally start at 9.30 every morning, but on Day 1 you should aim to get Charlie here by 9.20.
The finishing time will be 12.30 as usual.
We need the additional time because there are a few extra things to do.
[Q8答案句，答案空后checked 被动语态➕ 9:20但要提前，表示before the class] The most important is that we have a very careful check to make sure that every child's helmet fits properly.
If it doesn't fit, we'll try to adjust it, or we'll find him another one – but he must wear it all the time he's on the bike.
WOMAN: Of course.
(Q9) [Q9答案句] JAKE: Then after that, all the instructors will be waiting to meet their classes, and they'll meet up in the tent – you can't miss it.
And each instructor will take their class away and get started.
WOMAN: OK. Well that all sounds good.
(Q10) Now can you tell me how much the camp costs a week?
[Q10答案句（听数字） + Q10干扰项 去年数字] JAKE: One hundred ninety-nine dollars. （干扰项）We've managed to keep the price more or less the same as last year – it was one hundred ninety then. But the places are filling up quite quickly.
WOMAN: Right.
OK, well I'd like to book for …